[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_01_Quartermaster_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Feast to Famine",
        "Description": "Speak with the Quartermaster Saatvik Agrawal to find out if you're welcome in Corinth.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What happened?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ask five people, you'll get five theories. Some say we've been cursed, others blame the local Druids. \\n\\nSome are even calling for the town's leader, the Speaker of the Winds, to step down. But he's doing what he can.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Talk to the Quartermaster. If he says you can stay, then so be it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Spoken to the Captain, have you? He's normally not quite so dour. Although I suppose he was never a particularly charming man. \\n\\nIt's just that Windsward has just experienced a bit of bad luck recently.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_02_VisitInn_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Rest Assured",
        "Description": "Visit the Inn and speak with Innkeep Verildis Jannsen to check in. Discover an old friend at the Inn.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What did the Speaker do?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "He broke a centuries-old tradition and stopped paying tribute to the Sorceress Medea. \\n\\nShe hasn't been seen or heard from in decades, so many have questioned whether she even exists. Seems the Speaker decided to find out.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I really do appreciate your offer to help, but I must decline. \\n\\nCheck yourself in at the inn and eat a warm meal. Assuming you can scrounge one, that is.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Where've you been hiding? I was afraid I'd have to go back to the beach and search for you. \\n\\nNot that I wanted to stay here, mind you! This hamlet's ready for a bloody wake!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_03_VisitMarket_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Money Talks",
        "Description": "Visit the Trading Post and one of the Storage Sheds in Corinth. Then speak with Grace at the Inn.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What should I spend it on?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "There's a trading post here. Not exactly thriving, but you could at least get yourself some new clothes. \\n\\nI'm telling you this as a friend - you smell like something that washed in with the tide.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You have all that coin jingling in your pockets. Go and spend it! \\n\\nAnd you never know when someone might steal it when you're not looking.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "See, doesn't spending coin make you feel more alive? Glad one of us got what they needed. \\n\\nI'm gonna have to find some richer places to plunder before I can get myself a boat and get off this damned rock.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_FrancisTurner",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_04_SeeSpeaker_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "A Word with the Speaker",
        "Description": "Speak with the Speaker of the Winds at the Town Hall in Corinth",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"A message? What did he say?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "He said your heroics on the shore got the attention of this so-called \"Speaker of the Winds.\" \\n\\nSounds like a right charlatan to me. He's waiting for you in the town hall.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I won't be staying here long, but I'll make sure to leave a message when I head out. \\n\\nKeep your eyes on the horizon, my friend, and stay upwind of your enemies.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So here's the one Watcher Reese lavished such high praise on! A real charge-in-and-hit-'em-where-it-counts kinda fighter! \\n\\nWe need more newcomers like you in Windsward. Everyone around here's gone so damn soft!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_05_FixWindmills_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Desperate Measures",
        "Description": "Visit Golden Fields to gather food to resupply Corinth.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You don't think this is about the tribute?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Of course not! That damned sorceress doesn't deserve our hard-earned goods. But that was a misunderstanding. We sent the damn tribute! \\n\\nNo, I think this curse was brought on by the Druids. They were the first to transform into soulless Lost.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Look for Quartermaster Agrawal on the road out by the farms. \\n\\nAnything you salvage from the farms will be put to use, I'll tell you that!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, it's not as much as I'd hoped, but it's certainly better than nothing. This grain will keep us fed for a few more days at least. \\n\\nWith the windmills turning again, at least there's hope for the future.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Eyewitness Accounts",
        "Description": "Rescue and talk to farmers who survived what happened at Golden Fields.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll check the rest of the farm.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Your confidence seems matched by your skill, so I welcome the help. \\n\\nIndeed, if you rescue anyone you can find, we might be able to get some answers.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If there are any farmers, or Druids, I hope they can give us some insight into exactly what transpired here.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "That, my friend, was most impressive! These vegetables may make all the difference. \\n\\nI spoke to the farmers you rescued. They said you also rescued a Druid? What did she say?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Tracking the Tribute",
        "Description": "Visit the Iron Rose Garrison and find out what happened to the Sorceress Medea's Tribute.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The Iron Rose Mercenaries?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, they were hired by Medea herself, to protect and transport the tribute, but the town had engaged them for security as well. \\n\\nI haven't seen a single member of the Iron Rose Company since this whole thing started.",
        "InProgressResponse": "While I appreciate your help gathering food for Corinth, we need to know why the Company of the Iron Rose wasn't here to protect the farm. \\n\\n Go and visit their garrison.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I don't understand, my comrades were hardened soldiers. Tough bastards, one and all. \\n\\nWe've all died a time or two. What soldier hasn't on this island? How could every one of them have become Lost?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_07_MeetIronRose_success_alt",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Tracking the Tribute",
        "Description": "Visit the Iron Rose Garrison and find out what happened to the Sorceress Medea's Tribute.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The Iron Rose Mercenaries?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, they were hired by Medea herself, to protect and transport the tribute, but the town had engaged them for security as well. \\n\\nI haven't seen a single member of the Iron Rose Company since this whole thing started.",
        "InProgressResponse": "While I appreciate your help gathering food for Corinth, we need to know why the Company of the Iron Rose wasn't here to protect the farm. \\n\\n Go and visit their garrison.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I don't understand, my comrades were hardened soldiers. Tough bastards, one and all. \\n\\nWe've all died a time or two. What soldier hasn't on this island? How could every one of them have become Lost?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_08_RescueGideon_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Iron and Blood",
        "Description": "Rescue any surviving members of the Company of the Iron Rose and discover the fate of Sergeant Cotheran, then meet Leovix Silva at the Iron Keep.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You returned with soul intact?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, but I can’t be the only one! I've fought alongside these soldiers against impossible odds! \\n\\nNow they become Lost fighting some damn bugs? Sergeant Cotheran, tough as orichalcum! She must be here somewhere.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I just need a moment before I go and face Commander Merrill. \\n\\nShe will no doubt order me to recount every tragic detail.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "What a relief to see you again! I'm afraid that the same curse that befell the garrison has struck the Iron Keep as well! \\n\\nIt's swarming with my Lost brethren!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_09_DefeatCommander_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Commander's Correspondence",
        "Description": "Search Iron Keep to find any information about the missing tribute to Medea. Bring anything you find back to Leovix at the tavern in Corinth.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She didn't take the tribute?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "No, we received a missive informing us that Guard Captain Dupont had already taken Medea's tribute. \\n\\nIt was highly irregular. Of course if Cotheran had gone, she might still have her soul…",
        "InProgressResponse": "Do you have any information about the tribute? \\n\\nCommander Merrill would keep his correspondence on his desk.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You made it-- I almost called you comrade. Did you find anything in the Iron Keep? Ah, so there was correspondence from Medea. \\n\\nGood heavens! She never received the tribute. She is most displeased.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_LeovixSilva03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_10_TalkToSpeaker_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "The Missing Tribute",
        "Description": "Find out what really happened to the tribute to Medea by talking to the Speaker of the Winds and the Captain of the Guard.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So you think it's her?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I don’t know. But this is precisely why Medea entrusted the Iron Rose with the responsibility for the tribute. \\n\\nThe Company has never failed to honor a contract, and now the damned Speaker has tarnished our reputation.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I swear, if the Speaker doesn't own up to his mistake, you'll have to extract my sabaton from his arse.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You don't have to tell me, I already heard - that weasel Dupont let the tribute get stolen by pirates! \\n\\nNever would've happened with the Iron Rose! Now we're all paying the price, aren't we?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_11_LootPirateCrates_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "The Pirate Problem",
        "Description": "Travel to the camp site by Buccaneer Creek. Talk to Grace. Then look for Pirate Treasures at Buccaneer Creek.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So we don't need to recover the tribute?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I don't know, but it can't hurt. If Medea's not responsible for the curse, we could use her help. \\n\\nBut truth be told, I need a drink and about a week of sleep. I wouldn't make a good comrade-in-arms right now.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Don't forget to set yourself a campsite. If you get in over your head, it's a safe place to go back to. \\n\\nMy sword arm may not be with you, but my hopes are.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I see by your expression you realized the same thing I did. Didn't want to discourage you, but your tribute was all gone. \\n\\nBut tell me you at least found something of value!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_12_DefeatPirateCaptain_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Web of Lies",
        "Description": "Find evidence that Marcel was here with the pirates. Recover the stolen Verdant Gemstone.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Alright, we should check it out.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "If we find this so-called “Verdant Gemstone,” we could always sell it back to the town. \\n\\nOh, don't look at me like that! Fine! I guess if you're the one going in, it'll be your call. Surely, we'll get something for it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Think of that precious gemstone, all alone in that hostile place. It's a right heartache! \\n\\nOne thing's for sure, it's of no use to those rotters now that they've fallen Lost.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I must say, I'm quite happy to find someone here other than those foul pirates. \\n\\nAnd Grace mentioned a letter that referred to a priceless \"Verdant Gemstone?\" I don't suppose you found such a thing, did you?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Verdant Restoration",
        "Description": "Climb Mirador Shrine, complete the ancient puzzle, restore the gemstone, then speak with Nessa.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So there's more than one?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "There are four altogether. One is safe in the warren of Thornhall. We will need to find and restore the other three. \\n\\nBut first, this gemstone must be returned to its place in the Mirador Shrine. There is a catch, however.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Are you bolstering your courage? I find it helps to imagine something inspiring, like a big slice of lime and elderberry pie. Mmm... \\n\\nRemember, the sooner that gemstone is restored to the shrine, the sooner Windsward can heal.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, I understand all right! The two of you have decided to play noble heroes and save the land. And I'm leaving here nearly empty-handed. \\n\\nI'm the one who scouted out the Pirates, you know! I deserve something for my troubles.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Hidden Power",
        "Description": "Find out the location of the remaining Verdant Gemstones",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You could help us, you know.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh, so now you want to recruit me into your charity project. I'd refuse but I'll enjoy this. \\n\\nThat Captain Dupont was a right arsehole to me. I'll hang 'em both out to dry. I'll see you back in town.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I must say, I'm feeling much better now that we have a plan. \\n\\nAnd I think this has at least some chance of being successful.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Once again, you show up just in time! Can I see the map rubbing? \\n\\nAh, yes, I can see the locations of the two other shrines quite clearly.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_15_RecoverSpeakerJewel_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Secrets Revealed",
        "Description": "Stop Leovix from committing murder!",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can understand his anger.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, of course, we all can. But we need the information the Speaker possesses. \\n\\nYou'll have to convince Leovix to wait until we know where the other gemstones are. In any case, I'm in favor of justice but against violence.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Part of becoming a Druid is taking vows of non-violence. \\n\\nIf removing the Speaker really requires bloodshed, I'll be staying out of the fray.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So the Speaker himself had the second gemstone. How did I not see that coming? \\n\\nSaves us some trouble, I suppose. We can just take it directly to one of the shrines. What about the third gemstone?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_GraceWW_06",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_16_ReturnEldergateJewel_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Verdant Connections",
        "Description": "Return the Verdant Gemstone to Eldergate by climbing to the top of the ruins.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll go restore the second gemstone.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You read my mind! Yes, this gemstone should be taken back to the Spire of Kochab to the southwest. \\n\\nDo be careful if you run into any Ancient Guardians there. I'm afraid you're quite indispensible at this point.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I hear something new on the wind. I believe it's the sound of… yes, it's the sound of procrastination! \\n\\nA little Druid humor. But the gemstone does need to get to its altar.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well look at you, breathing life back into this wee, sad town. You almost make me want to pitch in. \\n\\nBut I've been anchored here too long. It's time to catch some wind and find more favorable surroundings.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower06",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_17_RecoverStolenJewel_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Jewel of the Sea",
        "Description": "Talk to Nessa near the Pirate Den known as Hecker's Haven. Then enter the Den and challenge Captain Korrapati to recover the third Verdant Gemstone.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"This town still needs us.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You've got it covered. And I’m starting to grow moss on my backside. \\n\\nYou'll need to be going after that third gemstone! That pretty little Druid wants you to meet her to the east. She's scouting out that pirate den.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Go on, then! You better not be getting sentimental on me.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Splendid! You clearly weren't eaten by the alligator. And you don't even have any rips on your clothes. \\n\\nNow I regret not tagging along to watch. It must have been an impressive sight!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_17",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_18_ReturnSiriusJewel_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "The Spirit Returns",
        "Description": "Return the third Verdant Gemstone to Sirius and solve the ancient puzzle.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Just glad this is the last one.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Agreed! While you head to Sirius, I'll visit town and make sure preparations are under way to resume the tribute. \\n\\nI'll meet you back here once I'm done. I can't wait until the land is restored. It's going to be marvelous!",
        "InProgressResponse": "It's very exciting, isn't it? Once we've restored the jewel at Sirius, the land can finally heal.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Did you manage to restore the third Verdant Gemstone? Strange, I thought I would sense something, but it's very faint. \\n\\nCould it be because I'm still just an apprentice? I have much to learn…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_SaatvikAgrawal03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_18",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_19_TalkToNewSpeaker_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Under New Management",
        "Description": "Return to Corinth and speak with the the New Speaker of the Winds.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should head back there.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You definitely should. But now that we've restored the third gemstone, I'm going to visit the Druidic Warren of Thornhall. \\n\\nI'm hoping by some miracle my fellow Druids are restored as well. I'll see you in town after!",
        "InProgressResponse": "When I see you in town, we'll celebrate with a slice of lime and elderberry pie. \\n\\nIt really is divine. It almost makes you forget the many horrors of the island we find ourselves trapped on.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Thank the stars you've returned! If the final gemstone has been restored, then that should mean we will soon have reprieve from the famine. \\n\\nI fear that hunger is quickly eroding the townspeople's patience with their new Speaker.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower07",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_20_LostTribute_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Abominable Luck",
        "Description": "Track down the missing tribute for Speaker Saatvik.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Was Leovix escorting it?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Sadly no. He's overwhelmed with the duties of Town Guard Captain, so he sent some of his new recruits. \\n\\nCaptain Leovix should be down at the gate. Please find out if anything can be done.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Please talk to Captain Leovix and do whatever is necessary to secure the tribute. \\n\\nWe can't afford another disaster right now.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Every time I have to see the terrible fate that's befallen my fellow Druids, I shudder at the horror. \\n\\nAfter all our work restoring the Verdant Gemstones, this is enough to make even me lose hope.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_NessaHarrower08",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_21_DefeatBoss_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "The Path of Thorns",
        "Description": "Infiltrate Thornhall, the most holy site of Windsward's druids, and find Medea. Convince her to give the region a second chance.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So she's mad about tribute and the shrines?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, and now she's the one preventing the land from healing. There is a fourth Verdant Gemstone within Thornhall, you see. \\n\\nShe has taken the warren for herself and removed the gemstone to ensure the curse cannot be lifted.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You are beyond brave to challenge Medea. Her power is truly staggering.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You'll have to forgive me. I've just spoken with the Sorceress Medea herself. I'm at a loss for words. \\n\\nI still can't believe that you defeated her, that this is happening.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "A Seed of Hope",
        "Description": "Travel north to Fisherman's Bend and talk with Yonas.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is that really necessary?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "No, but it would be diverting. You possess a rare power not found among newcomers to Aeternum. \\n\\nAnother possesses this power, but I will not speak her name. She’s the Herald of Corruption, and far more dangerous than you.",
        "InProgressResponse": "There is nothing more for either of us here. \\n\\nOur destinies lie elsewhere, but we may cross paths again.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Away with you, ghost. You'll scare away the fish. \\n\\nI remember you not and care not to, even if I could.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_success_alt",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "A Seed of Hope",
        "Description": "Travel north to Fisherman's Bend and talk with Yonas.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is that really necessary?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "No, but it would be diverting. You possess a rare power not found among newcomers to Aeternum. \\n\\nAnother possesses this power, but I will not speak her name. She’s the Herald of Corruption, and far more dangerous than you.",
        "InProgressResponse": "There is nothing more for either of us here. \\n\\nOur destinies lie elsewhere, but we may cross paths again.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Away with you, ghost. You'll scare away the fish. \\n\\nI remember you not and care not to, even if I could.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_FudeHinode",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_B_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_B_01_ReturnBrushes_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Brushed by Fate",
        "Description": "Return Fude Hinode's set of brushes to her from where she left them at Eldergate.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Looks like there's a label on them.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "If found, please return to the tavern in Corinth - signed F. Hinode.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The brushes are unlikely to make it back to the settlement without your help.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "My brushes! Thank you, thank you! I’ve painted so many places I forgot where I left them. \\n\\nI tried searching, but as soon as I got anywhere, inspiration would strike and I’d be painting with my second-best set of brushes.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_RoyaHakimi02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_IR_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_01_FindCreed_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Seeds of Steel",
        "Description": "Find and read the creed of the Iron Rose.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Training for what?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "To join the Iron Rose Company. Stalwart bastions of valor they are. I don't have a copy of the creed. \\n\\nYou look like a hardy adventurer. Could you swing by their camp and borrow a copy for me?",
        "InProgressResponse": "I know all the Iron Rose mercenaries. Commander Merrill, Captain Leovix Silva, Cotheran the Red, Gideon Sturm! \\n\\nSomeone should make small, carven images of them. People could display them on their mantles or windows.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You're back! I had heard that many of them became Lost. I was worried about you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_02_GetSword",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_RoyaHakimi02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_IR_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_IR_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_02_GetSword_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "A Garden of Iron",
        "Description": "Obtain an Iron Rose Sword for Roya.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Words to live by.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I agree. Problem is, I don't have a sword. And Iron Rose soldiers ought to have an Iron Rose blade. \\n\\nThey are very specific weapons. Can't be crafted by just any old smith.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I hear Iron Rose swords are weighted differently than most. \\n\\nTheir center of gravity is oddly located, increasing thrusting power.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "A warrior is no more noble or sharp than the iron of the blade he carries. \\n\\nNo more graceful than the way he treats others.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_GideonStormsbane02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_IR_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_IR_02 \u0026\u0026 06A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_IR_03_DeliverLetter_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "By Any Other Name",
        "Description": "Deliver Roya's application to the missing mercenary.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's gone wrong?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I wrote an application letter and took it to Captain Silva. But he's head of the townsguard now. \\n\\nHe doesn't want anything to do with the Iron Rose.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Thank you for all you have done for me. Perhaps it's time I embrace the path of all great bakers like… uh… I can't think of any to be honest with you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Darkness. Death. A baleful curse. That's all that is left of our order. Company of Lies and Ashes is more like it. \\n\\nI dreamt of defending the countryside with my comrades in arms. But they've all fallen now…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_TalesaSerrano",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_01_GatherAndRefine_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Supply Run",
        "Description": "Craft tools, then gather and refine the materials requested by Taleas Serrano.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"This famine is bad, isn't it?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Tell that to the annual tribute. That last collection was a kick in the nethers. \\n\\nOur stores have shriveled up like apples in winter. And it's not exactly safe to go collect more, is it?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Our stores are as barren as a gravedigger's prospects. \\n\\nHell, I'd even take green wood or flint. Anything just so our stores aren't so damn empty.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hey, look at this! Something approaching an actual stockpile, I haven't seen that in months! \\n\\nKeep up the good work. We have other empty spots where goods should go.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_ZhangHaoyu",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_TS_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_02_ForgeSword_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Fire Up the Forges!",
        "Description": "Craft an Iron Longsword at the Forge and bring it to Mason Zhang Haoyu in Corinth when you have completed your task.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"About the tribute?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "There's trouble with the tribute? I hadn't heard that. I was talking about the Lost overrunning the farms. \\n\\nSomething happened out there. It's not safe to leave unless you know how to defend yourself.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Open the satchel of ore I gave you, smelt it, then hammer out an iron sword. \\n\\nYou might need to find some timber first, but it should be simple enough.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Now, let's see your handiwork… impressive. Quite impressive. Either you've done this before, or you've got a knack for it. \\n\\nWe could use someone like you in Corinth, should you decide to stay.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_TS_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_TS_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "A Town in Need",
        "Description": "Check the Corinth Town Board to discover more ways to help Corinth prosper",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@06A_TS_03_LearnTownBoard_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_F_01_CollectJam",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_KathrijnJanssen02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_F_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_F_01_CollectJam_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Just Dessert",
        "Description": "Travel to Sweet Acre Farm to recover Kathrijn's Blueberry Compote and harvest Strawberries, Blueberries, Squash or Corn.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Rest? Safety? A day at the beach?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "No, dessert! Who could turn down some tasty treats? \\n\\nNo one, that's who! I have some ready and waiting back at the farm. I just can't get to them, it's too dangerous!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Those strawberries are going to go bad if you don't get to them soon! \\n\\nAnd who could resist some homemade blueberry compote!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You did it! You got the desserts! Oh, there will be a feast in Corinth tonight, I tell you! \\n\\nBut first, how about we try a little here?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_KathrijnJanssen03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_F_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_F_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_F_02_RecoverSpices_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Pirates of Spice",
        "Description": "Travel to the area around Buccaneer Creek and Mother's Tears to locate the missing spices.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where will you find such a meal?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm going to help make it! But first, I need something those pirates stole from me. \\n\\nThey've taken bags of my best spices! Honestly, I can't blame them, my spices do smell delicious. At least those soulless brutes have good taste.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I need my saffron, pepper, and cardamom from the pirates at Mother’s Tears. \\n\\nWith them, we can make even the blandest rations taste like a feast.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Sweet success! I can smell those spices from here! The fiery peppers, the rich scent of saffron, the warming aroma of cardamom. \\n\\nI'll have to save some for another batch of desserts.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_TsuiFen",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_T_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_T_01_DefeatPumas_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Predator and Prey",
        "Description": "Complete Tsui Fen's task to collect meat and fur from the Puma population in Eldergate then return to Tsui Fen's camp.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How many do you need?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You'd be surprised at how much meat I can get out of one puma! \\n\\nDon't slaughter indiscriminately, we need the local population to be healthy. Just a few will do.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I have mixed feelings about hunting puma, to be frank. \\n\\nBut Corinth is starving, so I don't feel as bad, so long as the poor beasts don't suffer.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Wonderful! This will make a pleasant change from all the wolf meat we've been eating. \\n\\nA little variety is good for morale.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_TsuiFen",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_T_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_T_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_T_02_DefeatBear_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "The Bear of Scratchrock",
        "Description": "Bring down the bear of Scratchrock Burrow. Report back to Tsui Fen when the task is complete.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Who died?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Another hunter, Albrekt. He was doing the same thing you were, trying to get more food for everyone. \\n\\nI imagine he got a bit too close to the bear den, but that's just speculation.",
        "InProgressResponse": "This bear is unnaturally savage. It has plenty of natural prey, so it shouldn't keep mauling passersby. \\n\\nPerhaps the endless cycle of death and rebirth has done something to it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Taking down that bear was no small feat. It's such a relief to hunt in the area, knowing it will be a while before the bear comes back. \\n\\nThough I'm still going to avoid its den, and so should you. No sense tempting fate.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_MichaelLewis03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_G_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_G_01_DefeatPirates_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Shot Across the Bow",
        "Description": "Sabotage cannons and light striped powderkegs on fire at the pirate stronghold. Defeat Shamgar then return to Michael Lewis.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's your idea?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You know how the Swarmancers destroyed the farm? Ruined the windmills? Made it hard to get anything done? \\n\\nWell, I plan on returning the favor to the pirates.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Damn pirates, think they can go around raiding decent folk with impunity. Let's see how they like having their homes raided. \\n\\nLet's see how they like shivering in constant fear.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "That'll teach them! I could see those explosions from here! \\n\\nWith any luck, that will bring us a spell of peace from the pirates.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_LionelDeLaRue02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_W_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_W_01_GetPatterns_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Warp and Weft",
        "Description": "Collect Loom Patterns and Fabric Samples from Sirius and Stoneview Seabreak.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What about crafting more?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Crafting takes time, and my method would be a bit faster. \\n\\nI propose we go in and steal the pants off of those ancient guardians. Well, perhaps not exactly pants, as they don't seem to wear pants, but you get the idea.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Every second you stay here is another thread frayed, another shirt torn, another cloth dirtied. \\n\\nWe simply cannot go on without new fabric and loom patterns.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "My thanks! How utterly divine! Look at this cloth! It has withstood the centuries and yet looks freshly made. \\n\\nIf only I knew the secrets of those ancient dyes… Such vibrant colors, they’re even more impressive up close!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_MargotEmerson02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_Z_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_Z_01_GetBisonNotes_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Zoology 101",
        "Description": "Margot is researching strange things in Aeternum. She wants to know why there are Buffalo here. Investigate the area and gather samples and any notes you find regarding them.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The buffalo?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "They are a species from a completely different part of the world from all others on Aeternum. There must be a reason. \\n\\nIf you head out to the west of Windsward you will find a herd of them. Collect what you can and bring it back.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Haven't discovered anything yet? That's okay. Take your time. The wonders of the world unfurl slowly in our fragile hands.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "What have you uncovered about our furry friends?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_MargotEmerson01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_Z_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_Z_02_SpreadJoy_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "A Wyrd and Wonderful World",
        "Description": "Margot has discovered a plant that seems to have strange properties. Gather sprigs of it and present them to people around Windsward to see what their reactions are.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You seem happy.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "More people around here would be if they glimsped the glory of Wyrdwood trees. Their beauty is trascendent.\\n\\nIf you find someone who is down, take them a Wyrdwood sapling. They contain the sparkle of starlight in their branches.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Wonder is a clandestine thing. It seldom shows its face to those who are in a hurry.\\n\\nIf you find yourself wandering, don't consider the quest incomplete. Think instead of nature unfurling her beauty to you slowly.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I see smiles on faces that were once dour because of you. To know that even one person breathes easier because of us is to have suceeded. \\n\\nI hope you remember that whenever you look on the potted saplings. That is true magic.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_ElricChapman",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_S_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_S_01_FindArcheologists_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "This Mortal Sphere",
        "Description": "A group of archeologists have gone missing near an ancient tomb. Follow their trail and discover what has happened then report back to Elric Chapman.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What spheres?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Pardon me, I was mostly thinking aloud. Just north of here there's an ancient tomb with strange spheres around it. \\n\\nWe sent a team of antiquarians to investigate but they have yet to return.",
        "InProgressResponse": "No luck yet? Oh dear. \\n\\nCould be they are lost to time - just like my mother's affection. Buried under sand and dust…",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've survived! I was beginning to worry. What did you find?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_ElricChapman",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_S_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_Z_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_S_02_PowerSpheres_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Creation Myths",
        "Description": "Elric has some interesting theories about the spheres. Follow his instructions and set them in place. Then report your findings back to him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What is it?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The spheres seem to store power. I believe that if you infuse them with enough azoth, they should be able to interact with other spheres nearby. \\n\\nYou'll have to find one that's more well preserved than those at the tomb.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We'll discover the secrets of the Ancients, you and I. That'll prove my worth. \\n\\nMaybe then my mother will say something nice to me.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've returned! Were you able to get a reaction from the spheres?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_P_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_01_RecoverTools_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Towering Tools",
        "Description": "Collect any remaining tools of the Ancients from Fallswatch Overlook and Mirador, then return to Antiquarian Pajitnova in Windsward.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What collection?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh, well, I am an Antiquarian. Yelena Pajitnova. Nice to... meet you. \\n\\nI collect tools used by the Ancients - construction tools - whatever they used to build these magificent towers. Only, I've met some resistance.",
        "InProgressResponse": "This view is magnificent, isn't it? How they built such wonders is beyond me. \\n\\nIf you'll recover any tools you can find, I might have a better idea.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You have a gleam in your eye... you've found something? Let me see! \\n\\nYes, these are precisely the types of things I'm looking for. The Ancients did not share our methods of construction at all.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_P_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_P_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_02_DefeatKisare_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Taken to Task",
        "Description": "Defeat Kisare the Taskmaster to acquire the Taskmaster's Heart. Then report back to Antiquarian Pajitnova in Windsward.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What kind of labor?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The kind you do with your hands. The funny thing is that we still don't even know what the Ancients look like. \\n\\nTwo hands? Four hands? No hands? But I believe it was not the Ancients themselves who did the work.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Whatever elements you can recover from the corpse of the Taskmaster would be of greatest interest to me.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Did you defeat the Taskmaster? Amazing! Let me see what you found… \\n\\nYes, the very heart of this being, clearly not just flesh and blood, but was he once human? This is the perfect addition to my collection! Thank you!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_YelenaPajitnova02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06A_P_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06A_P_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "06A_P_03_RecoverEyepiece_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Seeing Clearly (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Collect the Antiquarian's Eyepiece from Simon Grey in Amrine Excavation for Antiquarian Pajitnova in Windsward.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Who are you talking about?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Simon. Simon Grey, one of the most brilliant researchers on Aeternum. \\n\\nHe disappeared some time ago in the Amrine Excavation. It's sad for many reasons. Especially for the loss of his equipment.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You must think me callous, wanting Simon's Eyepiece, but I have already mourned Simon's loss. \\n\\nIf he has no more need of the Eyepiece, it should go to someone who does, like myself.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So it's true then? Simon Grey became Lost, his soul never able to be repaired. Very sad. \\n\\nHis research was groundbreaking, and I will use the Antiquarian's Eyepiece to honor his legacy. Thank you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0623_0101_FQ01",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0623_0101_d_00_container_FQ01",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0623_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0623_0101_FQ01_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Fishing With Shields",
        "Description": "Collect Woodlouse bait by gathering bushes for Master Fisher Shields. Talk to Master Fisher Shields in Windsward.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Hello, I'm {playerName}.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ahoy there, {playerName}! Before you get to the adventure and glory, you'll need to learn how to fill your belly with the bounty of the sea. \\n\\nFirst, you'll need some bait.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Have you found any Woodlice yet? If you look through the splintered remains of the bushes you've gathered you should be able to spot a few of the buggers. Come back to me when you have five of them.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Woodlice draw in larger fish, and believe you me, size matters. Beside that, though, there's still some more basics I want to impart to you, skipper.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0623_0102_FQ02",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0623_0102_d_00_container_FQ02",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0423_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0623_0102_FQ02_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Fishing Basics",
        "Description": "Cast, hook, and reel in three fish for Master Fisher Shields and deliver them to Master Fisher Ruby in Everfall.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What should I do next?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Let's get in on the action now! Fishing involves three basic steps: casting, hooking, and reeling the sucker in. It may take some getting used to but once you get into the pattern you can go for hours nonstop.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Master Fisher Ruby up in Everfall will appreciate seeing a fresh face to train.\\n\\n She's a real eager one, and has a lot of natural talent.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You caught these fish yourself? Shields was right to send you in my direction to continue your training. I've got so much to teach you!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0423_0101_FQ03",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0423_0101_d_00_container_FQ03",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0923_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0423_0101_FQ03_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Baited",
        "Description": "Catch one Snail in Fresh Water and one Clam in Salt Water to salvage them for bait for Master Fisher Ruby and deliver them to Master Fisher Clemenson in Monarch's Bluff.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes. Master Fisher Shields sent me to you.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "In fresh water the more common baits you can acquire are Snails and in ocean water, Clams. \\n\\nMaster Fisher Clemenson, would greatly appreciate this ocean water bait being delivered to her. ",
        "InProgressResponse": "Master Fisher Clemenson can be a bit rough around the edges but I consider her one of my closest allies in this strange land.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Did Ruby put you up to this? Bah! I don't know why she thinks I need the help...\\n\\nDon't get too cocky just because you got some bait.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0923_0101_FQ04",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0923_0101_d_00_container_FQ04",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1223_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0923_0101_FQ04_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Hotspot Hunt",
        "Description": "Catch fish from a Hotspot three times for Master Fisher Clemenson and deliver a note to Master Fisher Warwick in Monarch's Bluff.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What can you teach me?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Here's a lesson: Have you ever seen a spot in the water that looks like it would be prime for fishing? These are called Hotspots.\\n\\nTry your luck in these Hotspots and then take this.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Having trouble finding Hotspots? Look along the coast or at inland lakes and rivers. Hotspots can be found in any kind of water and anywhere.\\n\\nThere are patterns, if you can spot them.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "A note from Master Fisher Clemenson? Please, put it down right there. No, my hands are too dirty to touch it right now, but... thank you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1223_0101_FQ05",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1223_0101_d_00_container_FQ05",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1023_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1223_0101_FQ05_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Practice Makes Perfect",
        "Description": "Catch fifteen fish anywhere for Master Fisher Warwick and deliver to Master Fisher Perchal in Cutlass Keys.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I have something for you.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The best training is hard, focused doing. You've fished up some bait and a few meager samplings of fish, but I want you to fully commit to catching fifteen fish.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Don't give up now, recruit! Er, I mean, student!\\n\\nCatch fifteen fish for Master Fisher Perchal. She needs to eat!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Aha! Did you see that? I just fished up my biggest yet!\\n\\n...What's that? Oh, fish for food rations? I am a bit peckish.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1023_0101_FQ06",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1023_0101_d_00_container_FQ06",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0223a_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1023_0101_FQ06_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "The Giant Ones",
        "Description": "Catch eight fish greater than 20 inches in length for Master Fisher Perchal and deliver it to Master Fisher Park in Brightwood.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How do fishing and alchemy mix?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The bait, of course! What's your biggest catch so far? \\n\\nCatch eight fish longer than 20 inches, and bring them to Master Fisher Park up in Brightwood. She's a fisherwoman and an alchemist, and she's been experimenting with new bait types.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Remember, Clams and Oysters in fresh water and Snails and Electric Eels in salt water increase the likelihood of reeling in a bigger fish.\\n\\nAnything longer than 20 inches. will do for Master Fisher Park and her research.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Multiply by three, carry the one... Woah!\\n\\nWhat's that you've got? What a specimen! I've been studying fish lengths in relation to their weights and this one fits right in with my findings.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0223_0101_FQ07",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0223_0101_d_00_container_FQ07",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1323_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0223_0101_FQ07_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Fish Reagents",
        "Description": "Collect one Squid Ink and one Catfish Whisker after salvaging Squid and Catfish for Master Fisher Park and deliver them to Master Fisher Agarwal in Weaver's Fen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Can you teach me about fishing and alchemy?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Various fish, when properly salvaged, have parts that can be used in Alchemy.\\n\\nThe whiskers of the Catfish and the ink of the Squid most particularly. Could you collect some and present them to Agarwal in Weaver's Fen?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Alchemy in Aeternum is a delicate science that often relies upon elemental reagents. \\n\\nFishing can help acquire them.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "A new way to salvage Catfish and Squids? Why, this is brilliant news! Thank you for coming all this way to inform me of Park's findings.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1323_0101_FQ08",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1323_0101_d_00_container_FQ08",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1523_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1323_0101_FQ08_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Reel Life",
        "Description": "Catch three Slimy Boots in Weaver's Fen to clean up the waters for Master Fisher Agarwal and deliver a new line to Master Fisher O'Connor in Restless Shore.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What kind of fish are abundant in the Fen?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Shoes are most often lost to the swamp's pull, and if you could fish up five Boots that would at least be a start in helping clean up the pollution in the area.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Five boots, out of the water, and then visit Master Fisher O'Connor. Good luck!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I love to fish more than I love to fight nowadays, though I still do a fair bit of the latter.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1523_0101_FQ09",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1523_0101_d_00_container_FQ09",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1123_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1523_0101_FQ09_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Weapons of the Sea",
        "Description": "Catch a Fish Sword and a Fish Head Hammer for Master Fisher O'Connor and present them to Master Fisher Abebe in Mourningdale.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Agarwal said you had something for me.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The Fish Sword and the Fish Head Hammer are folk legends here - said to have been lost in these waters, long ago.\\n\\nThey're certainly rare finds. So rare that Fishing Master Abebe doesn't believe me when I say they're out there and itching for a hand to wield them once more.",
        "InProgressResponse": "While perhaps not the mightiest weapons, the Fish Sword and Fish Head Hammer sure are great conversation starters! 'Where'd you get such a nautical weapon?', people will ask, and you can reply: 'I fished it up myself!'",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hail, adventurer. I'm guessing O'Connor sent you my way to settle another one of our disputes... By Jove! Actual weapons fished from the water!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1123_0101_FQ10",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 45,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1123_0101_d_00_container_FQ10",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0324_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1123_0101_FQ10_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Treasures of the Deep",
        "Description": "Catch a Treasure Chest for Master Fisher Abebe and present it to Master Fisher Klaus in Great Cleave.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What can you teach me?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "In this land where rain pours eternal, there are many opportunities for fishing. There is something of greater value than the fish themselves lurking in the depths, though: Treasure chests.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The coin is appreciated, but it is the transformative properties of azoth here that I believe make the fish of Aeternum more intelligent.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hello there. Master Fisher Klaus at your service. You've got to be strong to take on the fish in these parts.\\n\\nThey learn to fight in these cold mountain waters, and you have to be ready for them.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1424_0101_FQ11",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0324_0101_d_00_container_FQ12",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1424_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1424_0101_FQ11_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Soulwarden Rations",
        "Description": "Catch five fish heavier than 30 pounds for Master Fisher Klaus and deliver them to Master Fisher Davies in Edengrove",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He's doing well.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The Soulwardens are hearty eaters, and need large fish to supply their rations with.\\n\\nCould you catch five large fish and deliver them to Master Fisher Davies? We both oversee the supply of food for the Soulwardens.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I mark my days with three square meals, mostly fish, of course.\\n\\nHelps me mark the passing of time.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Aye, that's it… Come to Papa wee little fishes… oh! I didn't see you there. Singing while I fish calms me.\\n\\nYou've come with the loot of a lifetime for the hungry Soulwardens here.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0324_0101_FQ12",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1424_0101_d_00_container_FQ11",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0724_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_11",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0324_0101_FQ12_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Azoth-Tinged Fish",
        "Description": "Catch an Azoth-Tinged Fish in Shattered Mountain and deliver it to Master Fisher Bernard.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What else is in the water besides fish?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "There are mythical creatures as well, like The Azoth Tinged Fish.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Don't be discouraged if you haven't yet caught an Azoth Tinged fish, those things are slippery and ephemeral at best.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, I assume you're the new fisher who Master Fisher Davies has sent my way? That is a strange fish you carry there.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0724_0101_FQ13",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0724_0101_d_00_container_FQ13",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0823_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0724_0101_FQ13_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Corruption-Tinged Fish",
        "Description": "Catch a Corruption-Tinged Fish in Shattered Mountain and bring it to Master Fisher Chang in Ebonscale.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Hello, Bernard. Anything else you need?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes. Help me prove something to my fellow Master Fishers.\\n\\nLike the land here, the waters are tainted by Corruption. I believe the fish are affected, as well.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If Corruption seeps down the mountain and into the southern settlements, then all the fish in Aeternum will be affected.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "What is that you bring with you, traveler? It reeks of Corruption... Mercy me, is that supposed to be a fish?\\n\\nMaster Fisher Bernard was right to send you my way.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0823_0101_FQ14",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0823_0101_d_00_container_FQ14",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0523_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0823_0101_FQ14_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Ecological Report",
        "Description": "Obtain various levels of fish fillet for Master Fisher Chang in Ebonscale to assess the health of the island's underwater denizens.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How are the fish of this area?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I want to do a survey of the fish in other areas to make sure they haven't progressed like the one you brought from Shattered Mountain.\\n\\nHelp me with this and I will recommend you to the Grand Master Fisher, Gaspar Machera.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We must survey the fish on the island to check for levels of Corruption. Then report to the Grand Master.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Greetings, young one. The tides spoke to me of your arrival. You carry fish from all over, yes? Yes, these are untainted. Good...\\n\\nYou've made great waves, little tadpole. The time has come to see if you can swim with the big ones.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0523_0101_FQ15",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0523_0101_d_00_container_FQ15",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0523_Fisher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "FishingQuest_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "FishingQuest_14",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0523_0101_FQ15_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "To Be a Grand Master",
        "Description": "Reach Fishing Level 100 and talk to Grand Master Machera in Reekwater.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Hello, Grand Master.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You must learn to think like a fish if you are to catch fish of greater sizes and legendary species. Beside me I have a list of the legendary fish you can acquaint yourself with on Aeternum.\\n\\nReach your peak mastery of fishing and return to me.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You are not yet one with the fish. Keep training, my minnow, and you will be rewarded for your efforts.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "At last you are one with the fish.\\n\\nYou have earned the title Master Fisher, and the respect of all the fishers on Aeternum.\\n\\nGo forth and fish and be well, friend.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "FishingQuestsArc",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0699_0103_d_00_container_BarkimedesPup",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20 || 04A_Side02_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0103_BarkimedesPup_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "Title": "Bones For Barkimedes (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Simon Grey's dog Barkimedes is awaiting his master's return and is very hungry. From what you can tell he would appreciate having some Ravager bones to gnaw on.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's wrong, boy?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Sniff, sniff… Ruff! (Barkimedes sounds like he's hungry.)",
        "InProgressResponse": "(Barkimedes is panting eagerly, waiting for the bones.)",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Woof! (Barkimedes excitedly takes the bones… and promptly buries them.)",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0699_0101_Barkimedes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0699_0101_d_00_container_Barkimedes",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "06_Quest_26",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0101_Barkimedes_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Repeatable": "TRUE",
        "Title": "Bones For Barkimedes (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Simon Grey's dog Barkimedes is awaiting his master's return and is very hungry. From what you can tell he would appreciate having some Ravager bones to gnaw on.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's wrong, boy?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Sniff, sniff… Ruff! (Barkimedes sounds like he's hungry.)",
        "InProgressResponse": "(Barkimedes is panting eagerly, waiting for the bones.)",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Woof! (Barkimedes excitedly takes the bones… and promptly buries them.)",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": "Daily"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0699_0102_d_00_container_Barkimedes2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0699_Barkimedes",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0699_0102_Barkimedes2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Repeatable": "TRUE",
        "Title": "More Bones for Barkimedes (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Simon Grey's dog Barkimedes wants an enhanced bone-chewing experience from the Enchanted Bones of the Shattered Obelisk expedition.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Hey boy, want some special bones?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ruff, ruff! (Barkimedes' eyes go wide in anticipation and his tail wags.)",
        "InProgressResponse": "(Barkimedes is panting eagerly, waiting for the special bones.)",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Woof, woof! (Barkimedes chews on the bones ravenously.)",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": "Daily"
    }
]
